Daniel Trotter



danielandrewtrotter@gmail.com



323 744 7735



linkedin.com/in/daniel-t-946617228

Summary

I have experiences with mobile app& web app development for 10+ years and also have experiences with leading the team(especially flutter engineers)

I have been following agile scrum 2 week sprint(some times 1 or 3 weeks), and have been managing CI/CD using fastlane/bitrise & github/gitlab, or Microsoft Azure

I am pretty confident to work/lead flutter project since flutter is my core skills with native mobile app development experiences

I do have experiences with building flutter packege/plugin using dart & kotlin/swift and also experiences with many state managements like Bloc, Provider, Mobx, RiverPod, Getx etc while I also like to use Singleton as well!

Here are some of my work result

Dating Platform

https://tabooapp.dating/

https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.tabooapp.dating

https://apps.apple.com/app/apple-store/id1235655086

Sports Betting Platform

https://sportsbetting.lv/

https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.deportes https://apps.apple.com/us/app/sports-betting/id591839871

Medical App

https://www.mytherapyapp.com/

Sr. Flutter Developer

https://apps.apple.com/gb/app/mytherapy-meds-pill-reminder/id662170995

https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=eu.smartpatient.mytherapy&referrer=utm_source%3Dwebsite-en

Experience

BairesDev

Jan 2019 - Present (4 years 1 month)

I have been working as a Sr. Flutter developer who is responsible on leading the flutter dev guys The project is pretty much common ecommerce app where customers can post their products, and delivers/carrieers can bring the orders/packages, and people finally can order/receive the products We have 4 mobile apps for sellers, customers, delivers, admin

There are QR code scanning feature for each products as well as orders, and there were tracking order feature and mapbox navigation feature for delivers, and much more...

Used techniques:

Flutter, Dart, Java, Swift, ReactJS, Firebase, AWS, GraphQL, MongoDB and much more

Flutter Developer

BairesDev

Apr 2017 - Dec 2018 (1 year 9 months)

Used Specs

Flutter, Dart, Bloc, Getx, Redux, Java, Swift, NodeJS, ReactJS, MongoDB, MarinaDB, AWS and much more



Sr. Mobile App Developer

Golden State Warriors

Jan 2014 - Mar 2017 (3 years 3 months)

I worked as a Sr. Mobile App Developer.

Overall years, I have been building 2 mobile apps using Java, Swift, Kotlin

The project is for sports professionals to measure their status (feeling, health, etc) and it can be reported life time to their manager and doctors so that they can plan in perfect way We also have some medical devices from SilverLab, and apple watch and google watch apps as well!

Used Specs

Java, Swift, Kotlin, .Net, Django, Python, AWS, Firebase, much more



Mobile Application Developer

Golden State Warriors

Jan 2013 - Dec 2013 (1 year)



Software Engineer Intern

Golden State Warriors

Jun 2012 - Dec 2012 (7 months)

Education



Tsinghua University

Bachelor's degree, Computer Software Engineering 2008 - 2012

Skills

Flutter • Dart • Java • Swift (Programming Language) • Kotlin • React Native • React.js • Amazon Web Services (AWS) • Firebase • GraphQL